miscommunication is part ii also turns off its times how to push poor in a very
沟通不畅是第二部分，它也关闭了时代，如何在非常困难的时期推动穷人
good job from it comes to interpret and what people say
口译和人们说的话是一项很好的工作
of understanding the reasons why they say it become a mistake is creating a
了解他们说这成为错误的原因的原因是
story a round specific situation which
故事的具体情况
we've as almost entirely right marcel thijssen consequences wifi lynn shelton
我们几乎完全正确，马塞尔·蒂森（Marcel Thijssen）后果wifi lynn shelton
or fendert in harrogate angry and trees and for
或fendert在骚扰愤怒和树木和
this phenomenon is colt taking thanks pursey mali in this video like to share
这种现象是柯尔特在此视频中感谢pursey mali的喜欢分享
some suggestions a wooden step is [Music]
一些建议是木步[音乐]
bonnie experience and emotional reactions caused by the words of other
善意的经历和其他言语引起的情感反应
people it means that will feel personally
人，这意味着会感觉到个人
effect all very essence is apt but this really the cache is it
效果所有的本质都是很贴切的，但这确实是缓存
problem s more to do with how you look at world than white world myself
问题更多是与您如何看待世界相比，而不是白人自己
history image or the world conform in
世界的历史形象符合
securities and lo self esteem what we look at things form that fountain
有价证券和我们的自尊心
well using reason you might be able to change that damage into
尽管使用原因，您可能可以将损坏更改为
something more realistic that spider first shoot jeffrey nose changing
蜘蛛第一次拍摄杰弗里鼻子改变更现实的事情
perspectives when you mac outside the fence all
当您在栅栏之外时的所有观点
about a week close your eyes to different perspectives
大约一个星期，您会以不同的视角闭上眼睛
so the key to getting out of this way of thinking is sine from my other point
所以摆脱这种思维方式的关键是我的另一观点
of view therefore essential to realize with the people around so so you mess of
因此，与周围的人一起实现这一点必不可少，所以您一团糟
even the as if therein securities thereby ssr hinderika thinking is the german skeleton
甚至似乎其中的证券从而使ssr hinderika认为是德国的骨架
view that the harbor in a modern the tea there was the world people aren't
认为现代茶中的海港是世界上没有的人
perfect many ourselves sns carlion red every one
每个人都完美无瑕的sns carlion红色
carries cheddar so what people say morning 6 more
载着切达干酪，所以人们还说早上6点
about them even then a byars as so in many cases people are really old about sense of
关于他们的事，即使如此，因为在许多情况下，人们对年龄的感觉真的很老
duty in it comes as criticism network for
责任来自批评网络
example import something and to realize that it's not about as you not being more
例子导入一些东西，并意识到那不是因为你不那么重要
about art performance in the workplace efficy de situation and from the company's
关于公司在工作场所有效情况下的艺术表现
perspectef we can make it less about eyes and more about the company of a
观点，我们可以减少对眼睛的关注，而可以减少对某人的陪伴
performance is truly beds and were better of doing something health
性能是真正的床，最好做些健康的事情
this 6 nothing about a fl usa young being you should be something that way the
这6个关于美国青年的事，你应该是那样的东西
side or even so learning reality fanfiction at the
或什至如此学习现实幻想
end of the day the views and the penguins of other people
一天结束时，其他人的意见和企鹅
are not up to watch what is up to was is howie react to them and that's where we
不愿意观察到底是怎么回事，Howie对他们做出了反应，那就是我们
go wrong very often it's important to make die sherman's film with green and
经常出错，重要的是用绿色和绿色制作谢尔曼的电影
rode flap processes and becomes streuli happening outside of was the mind 'it is
骑着皮瓣前进过程，并在脑海中形成弹道。
The camp's trickster meets reality by adding its
营地的骗子通过添加它来满足现实
own fantasy in the mix in this way simple remarks on
以这种方式将自己的幻想混在一起
someone could blow up your mind to the point with the hal universe is wambeek us
有人可以用hal宇宙把你的脑袋炸开，以至于吓到我们了
percy agent that is that she prays egocentric is this
她祈祷以自我为中心的自信的代理人是这个
discerning reality fanfiction doesn't mean that requires to know the ins and
辨别现实的虚构小说并不意味着需要了解事物的本质和
outs of the major in many cases will never know whether
在很多情况下离开专业不会知道
it's about being confortable with not knowing
这是关于不了解而感到舒适
instead of creating a reality a form of mindfulness would be a great way to
而不是创造一个现实，正念的形式将是一个很好的方法
check all this be caused by watching of pilot closely week and identify your
检查所有这一切是由于每周密切关注飞行员而引起的，并确定您的
fantasies and separation from reality 3 so earning janssens front tricks
幻想和与现实的分离3因此赢得了詹森斯的绝招
dismount similar to the previews one but it's different
卸下与预览类似，但有所不同
the previews of is about a thought processes this one is about what people
的预览是关于思想过程的，这是关于人们的思想的
actually c honestly many people are just feeling and
实际上，老实说，许多人只是感觉
the aren't derby intros has full in both cases there is
两种情况下derby简介都不完整
nothing to worry about and there is no reason to feel personally attacked the
无需担心，也没有理由感到自己受到了攻击
idea i had the in shot flowchart for the pool is that before i reject the
我有一个游泳池的镜头流程图，想法是在我拒绝之前
first ss of the perceived is truth or nonsense
感知到的第一句话是真理还是胡说八道
for a while, long must wibi set up but the trump card
有一阵子，必须很长一段时间wibi设置，但王牌
more about this could be an opportunity for learning
更多有关这可能是一个学习的机会
just as nonsense as long as wibi on sidebar 'janssens
就像边栏'janssens上的wibi一样废话
of course it takes time and practice to become more resilient against the words
当然，要花些时间和练习才能使单词变得更有弹性
will probably experience cells emotional reactions from time to time
可能会不时经历细胞的情绪反应
and that's okay lumen epictetus it's sun great advice
那没关系，这是阳光的好建议
on how to deal with people that criticize you know better rich de
关于如何与批评你的人打交道
trump to janssens and quote of anyone tell you that such persons bc love you
胜过詹森斯，有人引用你的话告诉你，这样的人不列颠哥伦比亚省爱你
don't make excuses but what they said you want and there i do not know my
不要找借口，但是他们说的是你想要的，在那里我不知道我的
other faults lc we not have mentioned oil die and quote
其他故障lc我们没有提到机油死机和报价
perhaps epictetus it says are the most fierce judo lessons
它说的也许是史诗般的激烈柔道课程
when it comes to taking funk soul personally the lesson to lose a lab and the
当涉及到亲自接受放克灵魂课程时，我们将失去实验室，而
led thanks slide info library or even last seriously were
导致感谢幻灯片信息库，甚至最后认真的是
less likely to feel the act but all those people say just look at you meant
不太可能感觉到这种行为，但所有这些人都说，只是看着你的意思
for mac os mac point of view and will see that were probably list significant
从Mac OS X的角度来看，可能会发现列表很重要
then i think tank for watching [Music]
然后我去看智囊团[音乐]
Yes Yes
是的是的
[Music]
[音乐]